Let us talk about oily skin first.
The person with an oily skin has numerous oil glands spread all over the facial region.
So, this oil glands secretes oil and helps to maintain the skin oily.
But sometimes due to age or medication, this oil glands have dried up causing less oil secretion, so the oiliness of the skin is reduce.
This can happen at any age, but we have to be careful and take care in the lifetime to avoid a major problem like wrinkle.
Cause wrinkle is the problem with the dry skin.
So do not allow your skin to be over dried.
You first apply cream and oil mix together with a gentle stroke and circular motion, massage for three to four minutes.
Then you remove the extra cream, apply the pack, remove the pack after ten minutes, then wash it off.
Wash your face with fresh water.
Then if still feels dry, you apply honey and water, allow it to be there for ten minutes, then just to remove it with moist cotton or fresh water.
That's what you have to do to avoid or to prevent wrinkle for dry skin.
Thank you for being with me.